Guide to the James B. Hunt Papers
James B. Hunt Papers
- Videotape, 1980-1984, 1987-1997, and undated
  - WBTV-TV3, Charlotte, Gore visit to Charlotte, 1992 July 30 (Box 12)
  - Gardner Hunt Reports, 1992 August 19 (Box 22)
  - WECT-TV, Wilm., Press Conf. on Ed/Gardner, 1992 August 4 (Box 12)
  - WLOS-TV Asheville, Gardner Ed. Paper/news clips, 1992 August 4 (Box 12)
  - WTVD - Gardner News, 1992 August 4 (Box 12)
  - Gardner Education Spot, 1992 August 4 (Box 12)
  - Gardner Press Conference/Education Paper Release, 1992 August 4 (Box 12)
  - Hunt/Gardner News Clips (Bad quality), 1992 August 4 (Box 12)
  - Gardner Ed. Press Conference, 1992 August 4 (Box 12)
  - Hunt for Gov., Economic Development, Hunt with Sheriffs on Prison, 1992 August 19 (Box 12)
  - Mecklenburg County Drug Courts/Gardner, 1992 August 20 (Box 12)
  - Hunt for Governor: JH-113, "Again", 1992 August 25 (Box 12)
  - Gardner Attack Ad, Hunt on Taxes (2nd Version), 1992 August 25 (Box 12)
  - Hunt for Governor: "Focus Group Reel #2", 1992 August 26 (Box 12)
  - Hunt for Governor: "Focus Group Reel #2", 1992 August 26 (Box 12)
  - NARAL-Hunt Press Conf./Gardner Econ. Plan, 1992 August 31 (Box 12)
  - NC Democratic Party, Slate of Candidates, Hunt Citizen Forum, 1992 September 1 (Box 12)
  - WECT-TV Wilm., Negative Campaigning, 1992 September 1 (Box 12)
  - NC Democratic Party, Slate of Candidates, Hunt Citizen Forum, 1992 September 2 (Box 12)
  - Debate Prep, State Employees/Hunt, 1992 September 3 (Box 12)
  - Debate Prep, State Employees, Citizens for Jim Hunt, 1992 September 3 (Box 22)
  - North Carolina Republican Party Slate '92, WUNC-TV (PBS), Gardner/Martin (Original), 1992 September 3 (Box 22)
  - Gardner for Gov., "Explicit" TV spot, 1992 September 8 (Box 12)
  - WTVD-TV11, Roy Lee Fox, 6PM, 1992 September 8 (Box 12)
  - Hunt for Governor: JH-115, "Truth", 1992 September 9 (Box 12)
  - Hunt for Governor: JH-115, "Truth", 1992 September 9 (Box 12)
  - Hunt for Governor: JH-115, "Truth", 1992 September 9 (Box 12)
  - WBTV. Gardner Crime Plan/Hunt small business, 1992 September 9 (Box 12)
  - Gardner Crime Plan Press Conf., 1992 September 9 (Box 12)
  - Debate Prep, State Employees, 1992 September 10 (Box 12)
  - Debate Prep, State Employees Debate, 1992 September 10 (Box 12)
  - State Employees Debate, Gardner vs. Hunt, 1992 September 10 (Box 12)
  - State Employees Debate/Visit to Rose High School, Greenville, 1992 September 10 (Box 12)
  - WCNC News, State Employees Debate, 1992 September 10 (Box 12)
  - WECT-TV, Wilmington, News on State Employees Debate, 1992 September 10 (Box 12)
  - WGHP-TV, News on State Employees Debate, 1992 September 10 (Box 12)
  - WLOS-TV, Asheville, State Employees Debate, 1992 September 10 (Box 12)
  - WRAL-TV5, State Employees Debate Coverage, 1992 September 10 (Box 12)
  - WSOC News, State Employees Debate, 1992 September 10 (Box 13)
  - WTVD, State Employees Debate Coverage, 1992 September 10 (Box 13)
  - WTVD-TV11, News Coverage of State Employees Debate, 1992 September 10 (Box 13)
  - WBTV Debate Coverage, 2 reports, State Employees, 1992 September 10 (Box 13)
  - WRAL Coverage of 9/10/92 Debate, 6:00 News, 1992 September 10 (Box 13)
  - State Employees Debate - Hunt vs. Gardner, 1992 September 10 (Box 13)
  - State Employees Debate, PBS-TV, Hunt-Gardner, 1992 September 10 (Box 13)
  - State Employees Assocation of North Carolina (SEANC) Debate, Hunt-Gardner, 1992 September 10 (Box 22)
  - Hunt-Gardner, State Employees Debate, 1992 September 10 (Box 22)
  - WTVD-TV11, Hunt Sheriffs Endorsement, 1992 September 14 (Box 13)
  - Hunt for Governor, "Focus Group #3", 1992 September 16 (Box 13)
  - WTVD-TV11, 6PM, Gardner Property Tax, 1992 September 16 (Box 13)
  - State Employees Debate, Hunt vs. Gardner-Rand, 1992 September 17 (Box 13)
  - WTVD-TV: Childcare Paper News Clip, 1992 September 17 (Box 13)
  - Hunt for Governor: JH-116, "Plan", 1992 September 19 (Box 13)
  - WCNC, 6:00 PM, Reports on Hunt Press Conference, 1992 September 21 (Box 13)
  - WLOS-TV, 100 Day Plan/Action Agenda, 1992 September 21 (Box 13)
  - WRAL-TV5, Agenda for Action, Bill Leslie 6:00PM, 1992 September 21 (Box 13)
  - Discussion, Hunt Debate, Hickman/Brown, 1992 September 22 (Box 13)
  - Overlay, Hunt Debate, Hickman/Brown, 1992 September 22 (Box 13)
  - Debate Prep / Thurs, 1992 September 24 (Box 13)
  - Debate Prep, NC Assoc. of Broadcasters, Hunt vs. Gardner (Carlton), 1992 September 25 (Box 13)
  - Hunt for Governor: JH-117, "Teacher", 1992 September 25 (Box 13)
  - Hunt for Governor: JH-117, "Teacher", 1992 September 25 (Box 13)
  - Hunt for Governor: JH-118, "Town Hall", 1992 September 25 (Box 13)
  - Hunt for Governor: JH-118, "Town Hall", 1992 September 25 (Box 13)
  - Hunt/Gardner Debate II, Sanford/Faircloth Debate I, 1992 September 27 (Box 13)
  - News Coverage #45, Debate, 1992 September 27 (Box 13)
  - News Coverage #46, Debate, 1992 September 27 (Box 13)
  - WBTV, 6:00 News, Town Meeting, 11:00 News, 1992 September 27 (Box 13)
  - WGHP-TV8, 6PM, Clash of Titans, 1992 September 27 (Box 13)
  - WSOC 6:00 and 11:00 News, 1992 September 27 (Box 13)
  - Hunt-Gardner Debate II, Winston-Salem, North Carolina Association of Broadcasters, Benton Convention Center, 1992 September 27 (Box 22)
  - Gubernatorial Debate, Hunt-Gardner, 1992 September 28 (Box 13)
  - "NC Focus Group Reel #5", 1992 September 29 (Box 13)
  - Hunt for Governor: JH-119, "Fair", 1992 September 29 (Box 13)
  - Hunt for Governor: JH-119, "Fair", 1992 September 29 (Box 13)
  - WRAL-TV5, 5:50AM-9:15AM, "Open," FSA Attack Ad Gardner, 1992 September 29 (Box 14)
  - Channel 8 High Point 6:00PM News, Gardner's Tax Law Suits, 1992 September 30 (Box 14)
  - WGHP, 6:00 PM News, Report on Hunt/Gardner Fair Sentencing Ad, 1992 September 30 (Box 14)
  - WGHP-TV8, Gardner in Grb. / Hunt in Alamance - Credibility -> truth, 1992 September 30 (Box 14)
  - WTVD-TV11, FSAct - Analysis, Bolick Report, 1992 September 30 (Box 14)
  - Gardner Press Conf., Drug Cabinet, 1992 September 30 (Box 14)
  - Hunt for Governor: JH-120, "Crime-Plan", 1992 October 1 (Box 14)
  - Hunt for Governor: JH-120, "Crime-Plan", 1992 October 1 (Box 14)
  - Open Net, Live Call-in show, Gov. Hunt, 1992 October 1 (Box 14)
  - Open/net Special Candidate Call-In, James B. Hunt, Democratic Party Governor, 1992 October 1 (Box 14)
  - WTVD-TV11, 5:50-9:15, 2 FSA - G, 1 - Hunt, 1992 October 1 (Box 14)
  - Hunt for Governor: JH-121, "Risk;" JH-122, "Education-Plan", 1992 October 2 (Box 14)
  - WGHP-TV8, Gardner Attack on BEP / Hunt Response, 1992 October 2 (Box 14)
  - WRAL-TV5, Conserv. Council, Clinton/Hunt, 1992 October 3 (Box 14)
  - Hunt for Governor: JH-121, "Risk-Revised;" JH-123, "Risk-Write", 1992 October 4 (Box 14)
  - WTVD-TV11 News, Victim Ad, Nineteen Ad, Ed End., 1992 October 5 (Box 14)
  - Press Conf. (Wilm) Gardner Commercial Fly Around, 1992 October 5 (Box 14)
  - News - Gardner Press, News - Hunt Press, 1992 October 5 (Box 14)
  - WBTV, News - Gardner Press, News - Hunt Press, 1992 October 5 (Box 14)
  - WRAL-TV5 News, Poll Results, 1992 October 6 (Box 14)
  - Hunt for Governor: JH-117, "Teacher", 1992 October 7 (Box 14)
  - Hunt for Governor: JH-118, "Town Hall", 1992 October 7 (Box 14)
  - Hunt for Governor: JH-125, "Family", 1992 October 7 (Box 14)
  - Hunt for Governor: JH-121, "Risk-Revised", 1992 October 8 (Box 14)
  - Hunt for Governor: JH-126, "Attend;" JH-127, "Business", 1992 October 8 (Box 14)
  - Hunt for Governor: JH-126, "Attend;" JH-127, "Business", 1992 October 8 (Box 14)
  - North Carolina Focus Group #6, 1992 October 9 (Box 14)
  - Gov. & Marie, Resp. on Business Ad, 1992 October 9 (Box 14)
  - Hunt for Governor: JH-127, "Business;" JH-128, "Economic-Office", 1992 October 13 (Box 14)
  - Hunt for Governor: JH-127, "Business;" JH-128, "Economic-Office", 1992 October 13 (Box 14)
  - Pope smashes Wickes on Taxes and Death Penalty for Cop Killers, 1992 October 13 (Box 14)
  - WTVD-TV11, 1992 October 13 (Box 14)
  - WTVD-TV11, Color, 1992 October 13 (Box 14)
  - Reports on Weed of Seed Program and Jim Hunt's visit to Charlotte?Aired: WSOC, WBTV, WCNC, 5:30 and 6:00 PM, 1992 October 16 (Box 14)
  - WRAL-TV5, 11PM News, Hunt/Richards Rally, 1992 October 18 (Box 15)
  - WTVD-TV11, Women's Rally - Hunt + Gov. Richards Rally, 1992 October 18 (Box 15)
  - WRAL-TV5, 5:45AM-9:15AM, Hunt UNC Rally/Negative Campaigning, 1992 October 19 (Box 15)
  - WTVD-TV11, 5:45AM-9:15AM, Hunt UNC Rally/Gardner DEP, 1992 October 19 (Box 15)
  - WRAL-TV5, WNCT-TV - Gardner Commercial, 1992 October 20 (Box 15)
  - Hunt for Governor, "NC Focus Group #7", 1992 October 21 (Box 15)
  - Hunt for Governor: JH-129, "Eastern", 1992 October 21 (Box 15)
  - Hunt for Governor: JH-129, "Eastern", 1992 October 21 (Box 15)
  - Gardner for Gov.: "Penny" TV Spot, 1992 October 21 (Box 15)
  - Hunt for Governor: JH-126, "Attend;" JH-132, "Dead Wrong-Revised", 1992 October 22 (Box 15)
  - Hunt for Governor: JH-126, "Attend;" JH-132, "Dead Wrong-Revised", 1992 October 22 (Box 15)
  - Hunt for Governor: JH-133, "On the Move", 1992 October 23 (Box 15)
  - Hunt for Governor: JH-133, "On the Move", 1992 October 23 (Box 15)
  - WRAL-TV5, "most dirtiest, neg. lowest", Gardner/Hunt Negative Campaign, 1992 October 23 (Box 15)
  - WSOC Project Vote Education, 1992 October 25 (Box 15)
  - WFMY-TV2, Gardner/Hunt Neg Campaigning, blame each other, 1992 October 27 (Box 15)
  - WRAL-TV5, Gardner Accusations of Spying, 1992 October 28 (Box 15)
  - Gardner for Gov.: "Folder" TV Spot, 1992 October 28 (Box 15)
  - Hunt for Governor: JH-134, "New Low;" JH-135, "Final;" JH-136, "Felon", 1992 October 29 (Box 15)
  - Hunt for Governor: JH-134, "New Low;" JH-135, "Final;" JH-136, "Felon", 1992 October 29 (Box 15)
  - WTVD-TV11, Noon News, Hunt/Gardner, Eavesdropping Allegations, 1992 October 29 (Box 15)
  - Gardner for Gov.: "Barrel" TV Spot, 1992 October 29 (Box 15)
  - WRAL-TV5, 11PM News and AM, FBI Story, 1992 October 29 (Box 15)
  - Hunt for Governor: JH-138, "Dirt;" JH-137, "Felon-Revised", 1992 October 30 (Box 15)
  - Hunt for Governor: JH-138, "Dirt;" JH-137, "Felon-Revised", 1992 October 30 (Box 15)
  - Gardner Press Conference - TV Commercial "Investigation", 1992 October 30 (Box 15)
  - WRAL-TV5, 5:30/6:00 News, 1992 October 30 (Box 15)
  - WRAL-TV5, Noon News, 1992 October 30 (Box 15)
  - WTVD-TV11, 11PM News, "Bugging"/Gov. + Marie II, 1992 October 30 (Box 15)
  - WTVD-TV11, 5:30/6:00 News, 1992 October 30 (Box 15)
  - WTVD-TV11, Noon News, 1992 October 30 (Box 15)
  - WTVD-TV11, 6PM News, 1992 October 31 (Box 15)
  - Gardner for Gov.: "Like That" TV Spot, 1992 November 1 (Box 15)
  - WRAL-TV5, 10:15AM-12:15, 1992 November 1 (Box 15)
  - WRAL-TV5, 11PM News, 1992 November 1 (Box 15)
  - WTVD-TV11, 11PM News, 1992 November 1 (Box 15)
  - WRAL-TV5 and WTVD TV11 Newscasts, 1992 November 1 (Box 16)
  - Rand-Gardner News Clips, Lawsuit, 1992 November 1 (Box 22)
  - WECT-TV Wilmington News, 1992 November 2 (Box 16)
  - WFMY-TV2, 6PM News, 1992 November 2 (Box 16)
  - WITN-TV 6PM and 11PM News, 1992 November 2 (Box 16)
  - WTVD-TV11, 11PM News, 5:30AM-9:15AM, 1992 November 2 (Box 16)
  - WRAL-TV5, 3:45-7:00, 6PM News/commercials, 1992 November 2 (Box 16)
  - WRAL-TV5, Noon News and "Marton" Commercial, 1992 November 2 (Box 16)
  - WTVD-TV11, 3:45-7:00PM, 6PM News/commercials, 1992 November 2 (Box 16)
  - WTVD-TV11, Noon News, 1992 November 2 (Box 16)
  - WGHP-TV8 News, 1992 November 3 (Box 16)
  - WGHP-TV8, 5-5:30, 6:00, 11PM News, 1992 November 3 (Box 16)
  - WRAL-TV5 Election Night, 1992 November 3 (Box 16)
  - WRAL-TV5, Noon News, 1992 November 3 (Box 16)
  - WTVD-TV11 Election Night, 1992 November 3 (Box 16)
  - WTVD-TV11, Noon News, 1992 November 3 (Box 16)
  - WRAL-TV5, 6+11PM/Gov. Hunt, 1992 November 4 (Box 16)
  - WTVD-TV11, 6+11PM, Gov. Hunt Interview, 1992 November 4 (Box 16)
  - WRAL-TV5 8-9, 1992 November 7 (Box 16)
  - Rindy Media, Demo Reel, 1994 May 1 (Box 20)
  - Steve Arnold, 1995 September 20 (Box 23)
  - Hunt for Governor: JH96-114, "Require", 1996 (Box 17)
  - Hunt for Governor: JH96-114, "Require", 1996 (Box 17)
  - Hunt for Governor: JH96-114, "Require", 1996 (Box 17)
  - Hunt for Governor: JH96-114, "Require", 1996 (Box 17)
  - Hunt for Governor: JH96-114, "Require", 1996 (Box 17)
  - Hunt: "Challenge," "Education II - Revised," "Economic Development," "Crime-Plan," "Education-Plan," "Economy-Office," "Jobs Town", 1996 February 21 (Box 23)
  - Jim Hunt GMMB Tape 1, 1996 August 12 (Box 23)
  - Jim Hunt GMMB Tape 1A, 1996 August 12 (Box 23)
  - Jim Hunt GMMB Tape 2, 1996 August 13 (Box 23)
  - Hunt for Governor: JH96-111, "Pay", 1996 August 28 (Box 16)
  - Hunt for Governor: JH96-111, "Pay", 1996 August 28 (Box 16)
  - Citizens for Jim Hunt: Rough Cuts, 1996 September 5 (Box 16)
  - Citizens for Jim Hunt: "Prisoners/Restaurant w/cover," "Guns w/cites," "Support w/revised audio", 1996 September 12 (Box 16)
  - Citizens for Jim Hunt: "Prisoners/Restaurant w/cover," "Guns w/cites," "Support w/revised audio", 1996 September 12 (Box 16)
  - Hunt for Governor: JH96-112, "Guns", 1996 September 13 (Box 16)
  - Hunt for Governor: JH96-112, "Guns", 1996 September 13 (Box 16)
  - Citizens for Jim Hunt: "Prisoners/Restaurant with CG," "Econ. Development Restaurant", 1996 September 19 (Box 16)
  - Citizens for Jim Hunt: Avid Rough Cuts, "Agenda," "Agenda with v/o," "Restaurant-Econ.", 1996 September 20 (Box 16)
  - Citizens for Jim Hunt: "Require," "Guns," "Agenda," "Agenda v/o", 1996 September 26 (Box 16)
  - Citizens for Jim Hunt: JH96-115, "Issues", 1996 September 26 (Box 16)
  - Citizens for Jim Hunt: JH96-115, "Issues", 1996 September 26 (Box 16)
  - Citizens for Jim Hunt: JH96-115, "Issues", 1996 September 26 (Box 16)
  - Citizens for Jim Hunt: JH96-115, "Issues", 1996 September 26 (Box 16)
  - Citizens for Jim Hunt: Avid Rough Cut, "Economic Development", 1996 September 26 (Box 17)
  - Citizens for Jim Hunt: JH96-116, "Issues-2", 1996 September 26 (Box 17)
  - Citizens for Jim Hunt: JH96-116, "Issues-2", 1996 September 26 (Box 17)
  - Citizens for Jim Hunt: JH96-116, "Issues-2", 1996 September 26 (Box 17)
  - Citizens for Jim Hunt: "Education/Restaurant," "Agenda 2," AVID ROUGH CUTS, 1996 October 3 (Box 17)
  - Citizens for Jim Hunt: JH96-117, "Up or Down", 1996 October 3 (Box 17)
  - Citizens for Jim Hunt: JH96-117, "Up or Down", 1996 October 3 (Box 17)
  - Citizens for Jim Hunt: JH96-117, "Up or Down", 1996 October 3 (Box 17)
  - Citizens for Jim Hunt: JH96-117, "Up or Down", 1996 October 3 (Box 17)
  - Citizens for Jim Hunt: JH96-117, "Up or Down", 1996 October 3 (Box 17)
  - Hunt for Governor: Aired Comp Reel, 1996 October 3 (Box 17)
  - Citizens for Jim Hunt: JH96-118, "Agenda", 1996 October 7 (Box 17)
  - Citizens for Jim Hunt: JH96-118, "Agenda", 1996 October 7 (Box 17)
  - Citizens for Jim Hunt: JH96-118, "Agenda", 1996 October 7 (Box 17)
  - Citizens for Jim Hunt: JH96-119, "Tough", 1996 October 9 (Box 17)
  - Citizens for Jim Hunt: JH96-119, "Tough", 1996 October 9 (Box 17)
  - Citizens for Jim Hunt: JH96-119, "Tough", 1996 October 9 (Box 17)
  - Citizens for Jim Hunt: JH96-119, "Tough", 1996 October 9 (Box 17)
  - Citizens for Jim Hunt: JH96-119, "Tough", 1996 October 9 (Box 17)
  - Citizens for Jim Hunt: "Progress," "Need," AVID Rough Cuts, 1996 October 10 (Box 17)
  - Citizens for Jim Hunt: JH96-120, "Desperate", 1996 October 16 (Box 17)
  - Citizens for Jim Hunt: JH96-120, "Desperate", 1996 October 16 (Box 17)
  - Citizens for Jim Hunt: JH96-120, "Desperate", 1996 October 16 (Box 17)
  - Citizens for Jim Hunt: JH96-120, "Desperate", 1996 October 16 (Box 17)
  - Citizens for Jim Hunt: JH96-120, "Desperate", 1996 October 16 (Box 17)
  - Citizens for Jim Hunt: JH96-121, "Real," JH96-122, "Need", 1996 October 23 (Box 18)
  - Citizens for Jim Hunt: JH96-121, "Real," JH96-122, "Need", 1996 October 23 (Box 18)
  - Citizens for Jim Hunt: JH96-121, "Real," JH96-122, "Need", 1996 October 23 (Box 18)
  - Citizens for Jim Hunt: JH96-121, "Real," JH96-122, "Need", 1996 October 23 (Box 18)
  - Citizens for Jim Hunt: JH96-121, "Real," JH96-122, "Need", 1996 October 23 (Box 18)
  - Citizens for Jim Hunt: JH96-121, "Real," JH96-122, "Need", 1996 October 23 (Box 18)
  - Citizens for Jim Hunt: JH96-123, "School Guns," JH96-124, "Close", 1996 October 28 (Box 18)
  - Citizens for Jim Hunt: JH96-123, "School Guns," JH96-124, "Close", 1996 October 28 (Box 18)
  - Citizens for Jim Hunt: JH96-123, "School Guns," JH96-124, "Close", 1996 October 28 (Box 18)
  - The Democratic Party - America's Values for the 21st Century, 1997 October 6 (Box 20)
  - Jim Hunt Tape, WMFY - Greensboro, News at 6-7:30-11:00, undated (Box 18)
  - WFMY Greensboro Debate News Coverage, undated (Box 18)
  - Citizens to Elect Jim Hunt, 2nd debate coverage, undated (Box 18)
  - "Eye on Education" Guest: Jim Hunt, undated (Box 18)
  - #43 Debate Coverage, undated (Box 18)
  - #44 Debate Coverage, undated (Box 18)
  - Baker AG Orig. 400, undated (Box 18)
  - Charlotte Observer Debate Coverage, undated (Box 18)
  - Clinton/Primetime Live, undated (Box 18)
  - Commercials - Overlay + Discussion, undated (Box 18)
  - Geoff in Charlotte, Minority Affairs, undated (Box 18)
  - Hunt Speech #1, undated (Box 18)
  - Hunt Spots, "All the People," "Working People and Together", undated (Box 18)
  - News Clips - Raleigh, undated (Box 18)
  - Sawyer Compilation: Sampler of political commercials, undated (Box 18)
  - 3/23 Hunt News Conf. Environment, undated (Box 18)
  - Democratic National Committee, "Deficit" DNC-1, "Hardware" DNC-2, "Teacher" DNC-3, "Arms Control" DNC-4, undated (Box 18)
  - Election Nite #1, undated (Box 18)
  - Election Nite #2, undated (Box 18)
  - Hunt at NC 400 Gala, undated (Box 18)
  - Jerry Falwell, undated (Box 18)
  - May 28-June 1, undated (Box 18)
  - Press conference, undated (Box 18)
  - Primary Day news, undated (Box 18)
  - Project Vote! "Let It Shine"/"How Do I Recruit Them?", undated (Box 18)
  - Robert Foxworth, undated (Box 18)
  - Jim Hunt Interview, undated (Box 18)
  - Hunt/Sawyer, undated (Box 19)
  - Brad Miller Interview, Jim Hunt Interview, undated (Box 19)
  - Hunt/Sawyer, undated (Box 19)
  - Jim Hunt "Real Issue", undated (Box 19)
  - Hunt Speech - Good Take, undated (Box 19)
  - #4 House Intelligence Committee, undated (Box 19)
  - 116: Stump, undated (Box 19)
  - All 3 Debates, undated (Box 19)
  - News Clips: 5/14-5/18, undated (Box 19)
  - Reagan/Knox in Charlotte, undated (Box 19)
  - State of the State, DOI Speech & Soc. Sec. (Helms), undated (Box 19)
  - Berlin Airlift / Charlie the Cabbie, undated (Box 19)
  - Jim Hunt 4D, undated (Box 19)
  - Rodeo Promos, Kathi Peterson, Brooke Shields Anti-Smoking TV spots, undated (Box 19)
  - Actual News Footage, undated (Box 19)
  - CH 7, 9.5, 11p. 5/3; Return to Jim Hunt Committee, Raleigh NC, undated (Box 19)
  - Clinton/ACLU (Moore) By Guiley Campaign, undated (Box 19)
  - Keefer/Cromer Communications: Spots Demo, undated (Box 19)
  - Newstape 4/13-4/16, undated (Box 19)
  - TV 11 news Spot - 1994 or Mosley-Pulley, undated (Box 19)
  - WRAL-TV5 6:40 Gardner Spying Allegations, undated (Box 19)
  - 5) News [illegible] 10/26, undated (Box 19)
  - Election Nite #1 - Channel 5, undated (Box 19)
  - Election Nite #2 - Channel 5, undated (Box 19)
  - General Election Debate, Associated News Stories, undated (Box 19)
  - label scratched out and illegible, undated (Box 19)
  - Union Label Slot Machine, undated (Box 19)
  - EWN Commentary (Dr. Jenkins), undated (Box 20)
  - WFMY Greensboro, News at 6-7-11, undated (Box 20)
  - Democrats for the 80's: #1 Deficit, undated (Box 20)
  - Directors, undated (Box 20)
  - Gardner at "Crack Hse." Responds to attack on Drug Cabinet, Hunt w/ Gore and Press Conf. on Ed Bur., undated (Box 20)
  - Hunt for Governor: JH-101, "Challenge", undated (Box 20)
  - Hunt News Clips - Announcement Day, undated (Box 20)
  - Interview, Roy Leefox/taxes, visit to Ed/Rose Hill High School, Greenville/N. Bern/Washington Area. Commutations Taxes and Education, undated (Box 20)
  - O-252 Gov. Hunt, 252 - Beilman, undated (Box 20)
  - T-30-25, undated (Box 20)
  - Union Label #627, Slot Machine #927, undated (Box 20)
  - WFMY-TV2: Quayle/Gardner Train Ride, undated (Box 20)
  - WGHP-TV8, High Point: News item on negative txes ad on radio taken out by NC Repub. Pty., undated (Box 20)
  - WRAL-TV5: "Eavesdrop Allegation;" 5:30/6:00pm news, undated (Box 20)
  - WRAL-TV5: Geddy Reports & "Color" from Gov. Hunt, undated (Box 20)
  - WRAL-TV5: Hamlet - Gardner Overkill + blames Hunt, undated (Box 20)
  - WTVD-TV11, 6pm news, Gardner Press Conf. on Ed. Paper, undated (Box 20)
  - WTVD-TV11, Hamlet, Gardner/Hunt, Overkill & Blame: Hunt, undated (Box 20)
  - WTVD-TV11: 11pm News + Early A.M., Lonnie Levitt/FBI Story/News, undated (Box 20)
  - WTVD-TV11: 6pm News, "Eavesdrop" Allegation, undated (Box 20)
  - WXII-TV: 6 + 11 Quayle Gardner Train Ride, undated (Box 20)
  - Begin 10/29 - 10/31, undated (Box 20)
  - Tape III Log, News Clips Sept. 20 -> present, undated (Box 20)
  - WRAL-TV5, Debate Analysis, undated (Box 20)
  - DMV Enforcement Special, undated (Box 20)
  - Helms Commercials, undated (Box 20)
  - Dollars for Democrats, undated (Box 20)
  - Helms and Hunt Commercials, undated (Box 20)
  - At the Threshold of the Tropics, undated (Box 20)
  - North Carolina High Country, undated (Box 20)
  - "Made in America" PBS Special (Hunt), undated (Box 21)
  - WRAL-TV5, Gardner Education Plan and Hunt Response, undated (Box 21)
  - Republicans for Hunt, WTVD-TV11, undated (Box 21)
  - WECT-TV, Victim of Fair Sentencing Act Ad and Hunt Response, undated (Box 21)
  - WSOC-TV, Charlotte, Gardner Crime Plan - Roy Lee Fox / Hunt Response, 2 stories, undated (Box 21)
  - Dot Helms Ad, undated (Box 21)
  - WSOC-TV, Gore Visit Charlotte / Hunt, undated (Box 21)
  - WXII Greensboro, C. Williams / Crime Paper Press Conference, undated (Box 21)
  - WTVD-TV11, News on Gardner Book Release, undated (Box 21)
  - unlabeled, undated (Box 21)
  - "Nineteen," Shirley Hardee / Victim of the Fair Sentencing Act, undated (Box 21)
  - WTVD-TV11, 11PM News, undated (Box 21)
  - WGHP-TV8, Gardner-Hunt - Senior Citizens, Senior Citizen Cabinet, undated (Box 21)
  - "Investigated" Gardner for Governor, TV 00:30, undated (Box 21)
  - Channel 11 at 6, Crime Paper Press Conference, undated (Box 21)
  - Jim Gardner for Governor, undated (Box 21)
  - School Prayer / Truth / Budget Cuts Original, undated (Box 21)
  - Jim Gardner for Governor, undated (Box 21)
  - WECT-TV Wilmington, NARAL Press Conference, Amy Green, Gardner Comment, undated (Box 21)
  - Hunt for Governor: JH-101, "Challenge", undated (Box 21)
  - WRAL-TV, $ Governor Race, undated (Box 21)
  - Open Net / State Employees, Jim Hunt Call-in, Candidate for Governor, undated (Box 21)
  - TV 00:10, Gardner Attack on Fair Sentencing Act, Hopelessly Liberal / Hunt, undated (Box 21)
  - WRAL-TV5 11PM News, WLFL-FOX, 10PM News, undated (Box 21)
  - Fox 10:00 News / WRAL-TV5 11PM News / "Dirt", undated (Box 21)
  - WTVD-11 (Boliek), Law & Order Series, Candidate Profiles, Hunt, Thornburg, Williams, undated (Box 21)
  - Tape II News Clips, undated (Box 21)
  - Australian Labor Party Television Ads, undated (Box 21)
  - Gardner 30 sec TV Spot / Original, Tough on Crime, undated (Box 21)
  - Charlotte Observer Debate Coverage, WSOC '92 Primary, undated (Box 21)
  - unlabeled, undated (Box 22)
  - From Ted; Jim Eldridge; Gary Pearce, undated (Box 22)
  - 10 Minute Cassette, undated (Box 22)
  - Unedited (Hunt) Coverage of Tornado - 3/29-3/30, undated (Box 22)
  - Tony Brown's Journal, Show #1425, "A Tribe of His Own", undated (Box 22)
  - Presidential Debate I / ABC Coverage WTVD-TV11, undated (Box 22)
  - Signs, Signs: The Economic & Environmental Benefits of Community Sign Control (Scenic America), undated (Box 22)
  - Gardner - Paid Television, undated (Box 22)